idea, rationalizing your decisions.
That's really important for me. I think
the problem is providing a rational
framework for people
requires you to be able to be
comfortable
being flexible, which is
not something many people are afforded.
I think you know it's this this
difficulty in us discussing
the details of how we rationalize
the the sort of multiple ways that we
allow people to define their own
conclusions or infer what they will.
It allows for people of authority to
influence hidden vectors of information
to permeate our spaces and and not in
like some crazy psycho way of saying I
mean it literally in the sense of it's
just people can
spread things good or bad. This this